Guide to the James Otey Bradford Papers, 1869-1919
Department of Special Collections
- H.B. Parsons, 21 Jan. 1891; 403-04 (Volume 1)
- N.C. Van Veckten, 21 Jan. 1891; 405 (Volume 1)
- W.J. Hancock, 28 Jan. 1891; 406 (Volume 1)
- H. Salmon, 29 Jan. 1891; 407 (Volume 1)
- H. Salmon, 29 Jan. 1891; 407 (Volume 1)
- W.M. Crocker, 29 Jan. 1891; 408 (Volume 1)
- E.J. Crowe, 4 Feb. 1891; 409-11 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 5 Feb. 1891; 412-13 (Volume 1)
- John A. Davidson, 30 Dec. 1892?; 491 (Volume 1)
- Fourth Auditor, 3 Jan. 1899?; 493 (Volume 1)
- A.M. McBlair, 3 Jan. 1899?; 494 (Volume 1)
- J.S. Tucker, 22 Aug. 1892; 1 (Volume 2)
- E.F. Smith, 22 Aug. 1892; 2 (Volume 2)
- F.M. Woodson, 22 Aug. 1892; 3 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 8 Oct. 1892; 3 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Stein, 11 Oct. 1892; 4-7 (Volume 2)
- Schiller Hasford, 19 Oct. 1892; 8-9 (Volume 2)
- S.D. Brastow, 19 Oct. 1892; 10 (Volume 2)
- D. Burckhalter, 1 Nov. 1892; 11 (Volume 2)
- A. Stein, 15 Nov. 1892; 12 (Volume 2)
- A. Stein, 15 Nov. 1892; 13 (Volume 2)
- N. G. Otis, 1 Dec. 1892; 14 (Volume 2)
- J. Buckley, 9 Dec. 1892; 15 (Volume 2)
- M.H. Hurley, 9 Dec. 1892; 15 (Volume 2)
- Fors & Co., 9 Dec. 1892; 17 (Volume 2)
- Expense item, n.d.; 18 (Volume 2)
- Fors & Curtis, 19 Dec. 1892; 19 (Volume 2)
- Expense item, n.d.; 20 (Volume 2)
- J. Grimaldo, 23 Feb. 1893; 21-22 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 2 Mar. 1893; 23 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 2 Mar. 1893; 24 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 3 Mar. 1893; 25 (Volume 2)
- W.H. Taylor, 6 Mar. 1893; 26 (Volume 2)
- Dan Cawley, 6 Mar. 1893; 27 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 8 Mar. 1893; 28 (Volume 2)
- S.M. Wells, 10 Mar. 1893; 29-30 (Volume 2)
- S.D. Brastow, 15 Mar. 1893; 31 (Volume 2)
- To Whom it may Concern, 16 Mar. 1893; 32 (Volume 2)
- G.D. Roberts, 16 Mar. 1893; 32 (Volume 2)
- Wm. H. Taylor, 16 Mar. 1893; 33 (Volume 2)
- F.0. Forse, 16 Mar. 1893; 34 (Volume 2)
- J.S. Tucker, 17 Mar. 1893; 35 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 17 Mar. 1893; 36 (Volume 2)
- B.A. Pryor, 21 Mar. 1893; 39 (Volume 2)
- J. Grimaldo, 27 Mar. 1893; 40 (Volume 2)
- T.H. Goodman, 28 Mar. 1893; 41 (Volume 2)
- T.H. Goodman, 30 Mar. 1893; 42 (Volume 2)
- History of the Mud Wagon 2 copies, one almost illegible, n.d.; 43-44 (Volume 2)
- Anson Gorton, 7 Apr. 1893; 45 (Volume 2)
- G.T. Nicholson, 7 Apr. 1893; 46 (Volume 2)
- T.H. Goodman, 7 Apr. 1893; 47 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 8 Apr. 1893; 48 (Volume 2)
- Anson Gorton, 10 Apr. 1893; 49 (Volume 2)
- Anson Gorton, 12 Apr. 1893; 50 (Volume 2)
- R.A. Wells, 12 Apr. 1893; 50 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 28 Apr. 1893; 51-52 (Volume 2)
- H.T. Greenough, 9 May 1893; 53 (Volume 2)
- Gerald Cullen, 9 May 1893; 53 (Volume 2)
- Nat Stein, 15 May 1893; 54 (Volume 2)
- W.S. Bullis Good on early W.F. history and early California., 14 Jan. 1896; 56-70 (Volume 2)
- Eugene Shelby, 16 Jan. 1896; 71 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Stein, 28 Jan. 1896; 78 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 25 Feb. 1896; 79-80 (Volume 2)
- Article "Suffer Little Children to Come Unto Me For Such Is The Kingdom of Heaven?, n.d.; 81-84 (Volume 2)
- M.K. Haimach, 5 Mar. 1896; 87 (Volume 2)
- Billy, 16 Mar. 1896; 88-89 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Stovall, 24 Mar. 1896; 92 (Volume 2)
- Sermon extract by T. Wingfield, n.d.; 93-94 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 7 Apr. 1896; 95 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Wells, 9 Apr. 1896; 96 (Volume 2)
- Rev. Father Riordan, 10 Apr. 1896; 97 (Volume 2)
- "The Rev. C.T. Parkhurst in The Ladies Home Journal Aug. 1895" "The Sorrows of Others" "A Pulpit for Ingersoll", [1895]; 98-102 (Volume 2)
- B. Weygant?, 21 Apr. 1896; 103-04 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 22 Apr. 1896; 105 (Volume 2)
- Dudley Evans, 22 Apr. 1896; 105 (Volume 2)
- J.W. Lancaster, 22 Apr. 1896; 106 (Volume 2)
- Burt Arthur, 22 Apr. 1896; l06 (Volume 2)
- Poem "The Moneyless Man", n.d.; 107-09 (Volume 2)
- R.A. Wells, 23 Apr. 1896; 110 (Volume 2)
- Rev. J.F. Collins, SJ, 23 Apr. 1896; 111 (Volume 2)
- Poem "Over and Over Again" Poem "Only a Woman" Article "Courtesy at Home" Poem "Earthly and Heavenly Interest", n.d.; 112 114 (Volume 2)
- Billy, 29 Apr. 1896; 115-118 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Edelhard, 4 May 1896; 119 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 5 May 1896; 119 (Volume 2)
- E.M. Cooper, 11 May 1896; 120 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Gumper, 11 May 1896; 121 (Volume 2)
- J.A. Hart, 22 May 1896; 122 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 25 May 1896; 123 (Volume 2)
- Poem "Sympathy", n.d.; 124 (Volume 2)
- M.E. DuBois, 29 July 1896; 125-26- (Volume 2)
- Poem "In The Woods" Poem "Collision During A Fearful Gale" Poem "A Last Look At The Glass" Poem "Where Are The Wicked Folks Buried", n.d.; 127-130 (Volume 2)
- R.T. Brow or Blow, 24 Nov. 1896; 131 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 5 Jan. 1897; 132-33 (Volume 2)
- Park Commission Golden Gate Park, 23 Feb. 18 197; 134 (Volume 2)
- J.H.F. Van Eucehut, 6 May 1897; 135 (Volume 2)
- Letter not by nor to Bradford, n.d.; 136-37 (Volume 2)
- C.H. Tilley, 9 July 1897; 138-39 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Sullivan, 20 July 1897; 140-41 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. A.L. Horemus, 22 July 1897; 142 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 27 July 1897; 143 (Volume 2)
- List of photographs, n.d.; 144 (Volume 2)
- Wm. Pridham, 29 July 1897; 145 (Volume 2)
- Wm. Pridham, 29 July 1897; 146 (Volume 2)
- W.F. Bailey illegible, 3 Aug. 1897; 147 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. Robinson, 8 Aug. 1897; 148 (Volume 2)
- Mr. P.?E. Feeney, 8 Aug. 1897; 149 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Krause, 10 Sept. 1897; 150 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. E. Hudson, 5 Oct. 1897; 151 (Volume 2)
- C.L. Harris, 5 Oct. 1897; 152 (Volume 2)
- List of books sent to Miss Swaney Cunningham, n.d.; 153 (Volume 2)
- Miss Swaney Cunningham, 15 Nov. 1897; 154 (Volume 2)
- G.B. Simpson, 15 Nov. 1897; 155 (Volume 2)
- P.S. Hardenberg, 16 Nov. 1897; 156 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine illegible, 14 Dec. 1897; 157 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine illegible, Dec. 1897; 158-59 (Volume 2)
- Oscar Edelhard, 16 Dec. 1897; 160 (Volume 2)
- M.B. Davis, 16 Dec. 1897; 160 (Volume 2)
- C.H. Holland, 16 Dec. 1897; 161 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 25 Feb. 1898; 162 (Volume 2)
- Emily Roberson, 25 Feb. 1898; 163-64 (Volume 2)
- Poem "A Bold Bad Bug", n.d.; 165-66 (Volume 2)
- Wm. Pridham, 22 Mar. 1898; 167 (Volume 2)
- R.H.W. Dwight, 22 Mar. 1898; 168 (Volume 2)
- Charley, 23 Mar. 1898; 168 (Volume 2)
- B. Weygant, 20 Apr. 1898; 169-70 (Volume 2)
- No Name, 25 Apr. 1898; 171 (Volume 2)
- Edwin Cramer, 4 May 1898; 171 (Volume 2)
- B. Weygant, 1 June 1898; 172 (Volume 2)
- Marshall Field & Co., 1 June 1898; 173 (Volume 2)
- Capt. Charles Lydecker, 7 June 1898; 174-75 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 9 Sept. 1898; 176 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 9 Sept. 1898; 178-79 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 9 Sept. 1898; 180-81 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 12 Sept. 1898; 182 (Volume 2)
- Expense item, n.d.; 183 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. Lathrop, 13 Sept. 1898; 184 (Volume 2)
- Aleck, Driver at Del Monte, 17 Sept. 1898; 185 (Volume 2)
- Mr. Juncker, 17 Sept. 1898; 186 (Volume 2)
- Mr. And Mrs. Gilmore, 17 Sept. 1898; 187 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. M.P. Miller, 29 Sept. 1898; 188 (Volume 2)
- R.H.W. Dwight, 30 Sept. 1898; 189 (Volume 2)
- F.M. Ackerman, 30 Sept. 1898; 190 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 30 Sept. 1898; 191 (Volume 2)
- F.M. Ackerman, 4 Oct. 1898; 192 (Volume 2)
- Charles F. Burton, 4 Oct. 1898; 193 (Volume 2)
- G.W. Haight, 6 Oct. 1898; 195 (Volume 2)
- Expense item, n.d.; 196 (Volume 2)
- Oliver Eldridge, 10 Oct. 1898; 197 (Volume 2)
- Gen. Marcus P. Miller, 10 Oct. 1898; 198 (Volume 2)
- Aaron Stein, 10 Oct. 1898; 206-07 (Volume 2)
- W.E. Gilmore, 13 Oct. 1898; 199 (Volume 2)
- W.R. Huntington, 13 Oct. 1898; 200 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 17 Oct. 1898; 201-02 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 20 Oct. 1898; 202 (Volume 2)
- J.B. Morris, 20 Oct. 1898; 203 (Volume 2)
- Receipt; Poem: "The Little Face Against the Pane", n.d.; 204-05 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 23 Nov. 1898; 208 (Volume 2)
- James Morris, 23 Nov. 1898; 209 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 14 Dec. 1898; 210 (Volume 2)
- E.A. Steadman, 27 Dec. 1898; 211 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. W.M. Fitzhugh, 28 Dec. 1898; 212 (Volume 2)
- E.A. Steadman, 11 Jan. 1899; 213 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 16 Jan. 1899; 214 (Volume 2)
- F.A. Reiser, 6 Feb. 1899; 215 (Volume 2)
- R.A. Wells, 8 Feb. 1899; 216 (Volume 2)
- A. Christeson, 8 Feb. 1899; 217-18 (Volume 2)
- W.D. Cleveland, 13 Feb. 1899; 219 (Volume 2)
- W.M. Mitchell, 13 Feb. 1899; 220 (Volume 2)
- Poem "Pine Knoll", n.d.; 221 (Volume 2)
- Wm. Pridham, 15 Feb. 1899; 222 (Volume 2)
- M.B. Davis, 8 May 1899; 223-24 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. C.M. Peabody, 9 May 1899; 225-26 (Volume 2)
- R.H.W. Dwight, 10 May 1899; 227 (Volume 2)
- R.A. Wells, 10 May 1899; 228 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. C.M. Peabody, 13 May 1899; 229 (Volume 2)
- Dr. S.T. Turner, 26 May 1899; 230 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 27 June 1899; cover (Volume 2)
- Mrs. Plant, 28 June 1899; 251 (Volume 2)
- H.A. McCulloch, 29 June 1899; flyleaf (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 5 July 1899; 231-32 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 6 July 1899; 233 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 10 July 1899; 234 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 11 July 1899; 235 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. E.W. Peabody, 11 July 1899; 235 (Volume 2)
- Letter not by nor to Bradford, n.d.; 236 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. E.W. Peabody, 12 July 1899; 237 (Volume 2)
- Capt. Adams, 12 July 1899; 238 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 12 July 1899; 239-40 (Volume 2)
- Alack, Driver at Del Monte, 12 July 1899; 238 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 13 July 1899; 241 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 14 July 1899; 242-43 (Volume 2)
- Billy, 14 July 1899; 244 (Volume 2)
- M.J. O'Brien, 17 July 1899; 245-47 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 17 July 1899; 252-53 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 18 July 1899; 248-50 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 21 July 1899; 254-58 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 22 July 1899; 259-62 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 24 July 1899; 263 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 24 July 1899; 264 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 26 July 1899; 265-66 (Volume 2)
- Birdsall, 26 July 1899; 271 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 27 July 1899; 267-69 (Volume 2)
- J.J. Valentine, 28 July 1899; 270 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. Peabody, 28 July 1899; 272 (Volume 2)
- Mrs. Foot, 2 Aug 1899; 273 (Volume 2)
- Billy, 4 Aug 1899; 274 (Volume 2)
- Letter not by nor to Bradford; Expense item, n.d.; 275-78 (Volume 2)
- Capt. 0. Eldridge, 14 Aug 1899; 279-80 (Volume 2)
SEPARATED MATERIALS
Oversize glass negative of a print showing stage coach in Cal. mountains.
One scrap-book of newspaper clippings. Some are articles written by Bradford.